Narrator: 3
Idioms
Narrator: 1, B
M: I was convinced the exam was going to be really hard,
but to my surprise, it was a piece of cake.
Narrator: 2, G
F: The government say they’re going to give everyone free broadband,
but we all know it’s just pie in the sky.
Narrator: 3, D
F: Come on, tell me what you know.
There’s something going on, isn’t there? Spill the beans.
Narrator: 4, F
M: Jon isn’t known for his honesty.
I’d take everything he says with a pinch of salt.
Narrator: 5, C
F: She wants to work part-time and get a pay rise as well.
But it’s not possible to have your cake and eat it.
Narrator: 6, H
M: I’m sorry, but I don’t think I can meet up this week.
I’ve got a lot on my plate at the moment.
Narrator: 7, A
M: I’ve never read any Tolkien.
Fantasy fiction isn’t really my cup of tea.
Narrator: 8, E
F: Nothing impresses the boss more than people getting to work really early,
so make sure you do, too, if you know which side your bread is buttered.
Narrator: 9, K
F: He said he never wanted the job,
but I think that’s just sour grapes because he didn’t get it.
Narrator: 10, J
M: Our trip to New York was absolutely perfect,
and being upgraded to business class on the way back was the icing on the cake.
Narrator: 11, I
F: I’m afraid the latest figures aren’t very good.
To put it in a nutshell, we’re bankrupt.